

# MAISAM KARRABI

SENIOR BIOMEDICAL ENGINEER

# **PROFILE**

After 16 years of work in medical, petrochemical and industrial fields as engineer and leader, I can easily say that I am an experienced person and a decision maker.

Also, if I would like to say about my unique abilities, I can say that I am the creator of the algorithm and problem solving engineer, and I'm not afraid of any technical problem. I analyze the systems and always look for new knowledge and experiences.

# **KONTAKT**

phone:

+98(0)912-217-1107

E-mail:

maisamkarrabi@yahoo.com

#### **CURRENT LOCATION**

Iran, Tehran Willing to relocate

# **WORK EXPERIENCES**

#### "Iranian institutional investors association" CEO

2018 -

Now

improve the efficiency of the Securities Market, to expand professional collaboration between members and manage relationships between members of the Association in accordance with this Articles of Association "Farmateb Co." Technical Manager 2015 – 2018

Manage service engineers for after sales support of medical and laboratory-sold instruments. Works with Mindray (Chinese brand), TCOAG (French brand), Stago (French Brand) and Linear (Spanish brand). Also responsible for sales department technical support.

# "Petro Polymer Shargh Co." Managing Director

2013 - 2015

Coordination with foreign companies (Bandera and Sorema (Italian brands)) to set up production lines.

Preparing factory conditions for installation of production line. "PET" Production Planning and Quality Control.

# "Nepta Co." Project Manager

2012 - 2013

Leadership of oil exploration, drilling and extraction projects.

## "ATC Co." Technical Manager

2005 - 2012

Service manager and engineer for after-sales support of medical, petrochemical and industrial equipment. Works with analytik-jena (German brand), Miele (German brand), R. Wolf (German brand), EMS (Swiss brand), Somatics (US brand) and Waldner (German brand).

Also responsible for the sales department's technical and advisory support.

#### "analytik-jena GmbH"

•	Middle East service manager	2009 – 2012
•	Member of after sales support core team	2010 – 2012
•	Senior Service engineer 2012	2010 –

# "Fardavar Co." Technical Manager

2002 - 2005

Manage service engineers for after sales support of medical and laboratory-sold instruments.

## **EDUCATIONS**

# Islamic Azad University, Tehran

**Master of Executive Management** 

September 2012 - June 2014

M.Sc. thesis on "Simulation of a Successful Factory Structure in MATLAB and C++ Software by using artificial neural network technique"

G. P. A.: 16.80 on a scale of 20

# Sahand University of Technology, Tabriz

**B.Sc.** in Medical Engineering

September 1998 – June 2002

B.Sc. thesis on "Noise remove from 16 frames movie by Artificial Neural Network (Self organized Map) Written by MATLAB and C++ Software"

G. P. A.: 17.40 on a scale of 20

## IT Skills

- ✓ C++ and Turbo C, Professional
- ✓ MATLAB, Professional
- ✓ Office utilities, Professional
- ✓ Corel draw, Professional
- ✓ Delphi and turbo Pascal, intermediate
- ✓ Confluence software
- ✓ Seismic software
- ✓ Python, professional
- ✓ Artificial neural network, algorithm creation, professional
- ✓ SQL, professional

# Language skills

- ✓ English, Fluent
- Persian, Mother language
- ✓ German, Intermediate

# **CERTIFICATES AND LICENCES**

hematology analyzers	Mindray Co.	China
Coagulation analyzers	Stago Co.	France
Optical spectroscopy	Analytik-Jena	Germany
sum parameters and elemental analysis	Analytik-Jena	Germany
Elemental analyzer	Analytik-Jena	Germany
Microwave digestion	Analytik-Jena	Germany
spectrophotometer	Analytik-Jena	Germany
Atomic absorption	Analytik-Jena	Germany
sum parameters and elemental analysis	Analytik-Jena	Germany
Elemental analyzer	Analytik-Jena	Germany
Continuum source Atomic absorption	Analytik-Jena	Germany
Microwave digestion	Analytik-Jena	Germany
sum parameters and elemental analysis	Analytik-Jena	Germany
Continuum source Atomic absorption	Analytik-Jena	Germany
Elemental analyzer	Analytik-Jena	Germany
Atomic absorption	Analytik-Jena	Dubai
chemistry assay analyzer	Assel	Italy
	Coagulation analyzers Optical spectroscopy sum parameters and elemental analysis Elemental analyzer Microwave digestion spectrophotometer Atomic absorption sum parameters and elemental analysis Elemental analyzer Continuum source Atomic absorption Microwave digestion sum parameters and elemental analysis Continuum source Atomic absorption Elemental analyzer Atomic absorption Elemental analyzer Atomic absorption chemistry assay	Coagulation analyzers Optical spectroscopy Sum parameters and elemental analysis Elemental analyzer Analytik-Jena Microwave digestion Analytik-Jena Atomic absorption Analytik-Jena Analytik-Jena Analytik-Jena Analytik-Jena Analytik-Jena Analytik-Jena Analytik-Jena Analytik-Jena Analytik-Jena Continuum Source Atomic absorption Analytik-Jena

# **HONORS AND AWARDS**

Ranked 104th in the National University entrance examination (1998)

Being accepted to NODET (National Organization for the Development of Exceptional Talents) Entrance Exam to attend a 7-year program under supervision of the country's president (September 1990)

Third place for the Khwarizmi Youth Prize (Youth Innovation Festival) (Developing a new method to calculate the Earth gravity written with Turbo C software)